Steen, Ivan; Papers apap219
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Oral History and Research Files, 1936-2012; Undated; 1; 3.89 cubic ft.
  - POW, Japan and World War II POWs, Newsclippings, and Memoirs, John Browe, and Far East POWs, 1971; 1975; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - POW, Prisoners of War Bibliography, 1985; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - POW Prisoners of War by W.P. Skelton, 1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - POW Sandy: Death March Survivor and Search for Truth by Lysle Lewis, Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - POW, 42nd Annual National Convention of American Ex-POWs Program, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Proctor's Theatre, Correspondence, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Radio, Dolores Carrara Interview, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Radio, Interview with Dolores Carrara (1 of 2), 2004 November 11 (Cassette 104)
  - Radio, Interview with Dolores Carrara (2 of 2), 2004 November 11 (Cassette 105)
  - Radio, Edward Dahlstedt Interview, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Radio, Interview with Edward Dahlstedt (1 of 2), 2004 July 29 (Cassette 106)
  - Radio, Interview with Edward Dahlstedt (2 of 2), 2004 July 29 (Cassette 107)
  - Radio, Jack Hotchkiss Interview, [RESTRICTED], 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Radio, Interview with Jack Hotchkiss, [RESTRICTED], 2005 April 11 (Cassette 108)
  - Radio, Louise Marshall Interview, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Radio, Interview with Louise Marshall (1 of 2), 2004 November 11 (Cassette 109)
  - Radio, Interview with Louise Marshall (2 of 2), 2004 November 11 (Cassette 110)
  - Radio, Margaret Miller Interview, 1949-2004; Undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Radio, Interview with Margaret Miller, 2004 May 24 (Cassette 111)
  - Ralph Ciccarelli Interview, [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Interview with Ralph Ciccarelli, [RESTRICTED] (1 of 2), ca. 1981 (Cassette 112)
  - Interview with Ralph Ciccarelli, [RESTRICTED] (2 of 2), ca. 1981 (Cassette 113)
  - Record of 1936 Legislature (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Record of NYS Legislature, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Record of NYS Legislature, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Record of NYS Legislature, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Record of NYS Legislature, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Record of NYS Legislature, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Rena Button Interview, [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Interview with Rena Button, RESTRICT, 1984 February 29 (Cassette 114)
  - Rockefeller, Alton Marshall Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Correspondence, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Daniel Dalrymple, Interviews, Memoir, Correspondence, and Notes (1 of 4), 1982-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Daniel Dalrymple, Interviews, Memoir, Correspondence, and Notes (2 of 4), 1982-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Daniel Dalrymple, Interviews, Memoir, Correspondence, and Notes (3 of 4), 1982-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Daniel Dalrymple, Interviews, Memoir, Correspondence, and Notes (4 of 4), 1982-1984; Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (1 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 115)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (2 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 116)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (3 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 117)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (4 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 118)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (5 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 119)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (6 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 120)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (7 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 121)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (8 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 122)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (9 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 123)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Daniel Dalrymple (10 of 10), 1983 (Cassette 124)
  - Rockefeller, Edward Logue, Interviews and Correspondence (1 of 5), 1983-1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Edward Logue, Interviews and Correspondence (2 of 5), 1983-1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Rockefeller, Edward Logue, Interviews and Correspondence (3 of 5), 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Edward Logue, Interviews and Correspondence (4 of 5), 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Edward Logue, Interviews and Correspondence (5 of 5), 1983-1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (1 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 125)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (2 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 126)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (3 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 127)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (4 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 128)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (5 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 129)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (6 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 130)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (7 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 131)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (8 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 132)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (9 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 133)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (10 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 134)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (11 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 135)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (12 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 136)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (13 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 137)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (14 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 138)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (15 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 139)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (16 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 140)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (17 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 141)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (18 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 142)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (19 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 143)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (20 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 144)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (21 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 145)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Edward Logue (22 of 22), 1983-1991 (Cassette 146)
  - Rockefeller, Former Governor Malcolm Wilson Interviews, Notes, and Correspondence (1 of 2), 1982-1984; 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller, Former Governor Malcolm Wilson Interviews, Notes, and Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982-1984; 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (1 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 147)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (2 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 148)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (3 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 149)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (4 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 150)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (5 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 151)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (6 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 152)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (7 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 153)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (8 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 154)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (9 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 155)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (10 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 156)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (11 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 157)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Former Governor Malcolm Wilson (12 of 12), 1983-1984 (Cassette 158)
  - Rockefeller, Human Subject Review, 1982-1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller, Joseph Swidler, [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Rockefeller, Interview with Joseph Swidler, [RESTRICTED] (1 of 2), 1982 December 11 (Cassette 159)
  - Rockefeller, Interview with Joseph Swidler, [RESTRICTED] (2 of 2), 1982 December 11 (Cassette 160)
  - Rockefeller, Neil Moylan Interview, Correspondence, and Notes, 1982-1984; Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Neil Moylan (1 of 4), 1984 (Cassette 161)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Neil Moylan (2 of 4), 1984 (Cassette 162)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Neil Moylan (3 of 4), 1984 (Cassette 163)
  - Rockefeller, Interviews with Neil Moylan (4 of 4), 1984 (Cassette 164)
  - Rockefeller, Project Background Materials, 1968; 1976; 1983; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Robert Helsby Correspondence and Interview, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller, Interview with Robert Helsby (1 of 2), 1982 December 11 (Cassette 165)
  - Rockefeller, Interview with Robert Helsby (2 of 2), 1982 December 11 (Cassette 166)
  - Rockefeller, Robert McManus Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, "Rockefeller in Retrospect" Conference, 1982 December 10-11 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Ronald Grele, Correspondence about Consulting, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Siena College, Fr. Ben Kuhn Interview, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - South End Scene, 1984; Undated (Flat-file 1)
  - "A Strategic Plan for the New York State Museum" and Correspondence, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Victor Lord, Interviews and Articles, [RESTRICTED], 1984; 1987; Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Interview with Victor Lord, [RESTRICTED] (1 of 2), 1984 March 08 (Cassette 167)
  - Interview with Victor Lord, [RESTRICTED] (2 of 2), 1984 March 08 (Cassette 168)
  - Vote on Constitutional Amendments, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - WGY Interview of Ivan Steen, 1984 December 27 (Cassette 169)
- University at Albany History Department, 1965-2013; Undated; 2; 1.4 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains material related to the University at Albany's History Department and the Graduate Public History programs. There are large amount of memorandum sent out by the department as well as material about undergraduate and graduate committees. There are also multiple files about HIS 497, which is the department's honors program seminar class. There is one folder pertaining to the University's Social Studies Department.
  Several files in this series document the establishment of the Master's in Public History Program directed by Ivan Steen. Materials include correspondence, program overviews, and newsletters. There also is a file related to the 19th Annual Conference of the National Council on Public History, which was held in Albany. Professor Steen served as chair of the Local Arrangements Committee and on the Program Committee.
  - Social Studies Department Bulletins, 1965-1966 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 1)
  - History Department Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 2)
  - History Department Bulletins, 1967-1968 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 3)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 4)
  - History Department Memorandum (1 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 5)
  - History Department Memorandum (2 of 2), 1969-1970 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 6)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 7)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 8)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 9)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 10)
  - History Department Placement, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 11)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 12)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 13)
  - History Department, HIS 497, Fall, 1974 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 14)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 15)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 16)
  - History Department, HIS 497, Fall, 1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 17)
  - History Department, HIS 497, Spring, 1975 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 18)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 19)
  - History Department Undergraduate Course Proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 20)
  - History Department Undergraduate Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 21)
  - History Department Undergraduate Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 22)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 23)
  - Public History Program Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 24)
  - History Department Evaluation, 1982 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 25)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 26)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 27)
  - Public History Program Overview, 1983; 1986; Undated (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 28)
  - History Department Newsletters, 1983-1984; 1987 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 29)
  - Public History Advisory Committee, 1983-1987; 1990; Undated (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 30)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 31)
  - Public History Program Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 32)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 33)
  - Public History Committee, History Department, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 34)
  - History Department Graduate Committee, 1987-2000 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 35)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 36)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1991-1992 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 37)
  - Public History Program Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 39)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 40)
  - Albany Institute of History & Art, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 1)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 2)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 3)
  - History Department Memorandum, 1995-1996 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 4)
  - 19th Annual Conference of the National Council on Public History, 1997 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 5)
  - Public History Program 20th Anniversary, 2002 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 6)
  - Rock and Newbold Scholarships, 2002-2004 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 7)
  - Public History Program Newsletters, 2002-2006; 2008-2009 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 8)
  - The FBI in Action May 1, 1943 Staging at Researching New York Conference, 2004 (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 9)
  - Public History Program 30th Anniversary, 2013; Undated (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 10)
  - Career Networking for History Students, Department of History, Undated (Box 2 (2-University at Albany History Department), Folder 11)